Sam Watkinson

Senior Strategist
Borne
sam@weareborne.com
07817690720
https://www.linkedin.com/in/hellosamwatkinson/

I help the humans behind brands connect with the humans who buy from (and buy into) them.Planner and strategist with experience across B2B & B2C, building brands for the real world.Doing some thinking, with a tilt towards driving effectiveness and using data to deliver insights.I help the humans behind brands connect with the humans who buy from (and buy into) them. Planner and strategist with experience across B2B & B2C, building brands for the real world. Doing some thinking, with a tilt towards driving effectiveness and using data to deliver insights.

Skills

Leadership, Problem Solving, Account Direction, Client Services, Account Planning, Consumer Insights, Focus Groups, Workshops, Creative Strategy, Advertising

Employment

Borne Senior Strategist	01/11/2023 -
Fountain Partnership	01/04/2022 - 01/11/2023
Senior Account Director	01/04/2022 - 01/11/2023
Account Director	01/12/2020 - 01/04/2022
krow groupkrow group Account Planner	01/10/2019 - 01/12/2020

bigdog Agency

Account Planner 01/11/2017 - 01/10/2019

Planner - Insight & Analytics 01/09/2015 - 01/11/2017

balloon dogballoon dog Client Engagement 01/09/2014 - 01/09/2015

Executive

Education

Durham University Bachelor of Science (BSc)